Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm
1918-1919
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. National War Labor Board (1918-1919)
5752 mf
2.44 cubic feet
22 microfilm reels
Microfilm, papers (documents).
Minutes, case files, and records of the National War Labor Board.
3337352
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The National War Labor Board (NWLB) was appointed by President Woodrow Wilson in April, 1918. Guided by the principles of labor relations suggested by the President's Mediation Commission in September, 1917, the Board's purpose was to settle labor-management disputes and stabilize wages during World War I. The NWLB consisted of five industry representatives (chosen by the National Industrial Conference Board), five labor representatives (chosen by the A.F.of L.), and two co-chairs appointed by President Wilson.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of digests of cases, examiners' reports, findings and awards, selected case files and proceedings transcripts, and executive session minutes documenting the work of the National War Labor Board. Also included are minutes of NWLB public meetings, selected administrative files and general subject files.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5298: IAM vs. Northwest Airlines and Miscellaneous others Arbitration Proceedings 5310: NWLB Records 5312: NWLB Files 5314: NWLB Non-Ferrous Metals Commission Records 5311: NWLB Region II Office Files and Cases 5313: NWLB Southern Coal Procedures Records 5699: William Bardsley Collection of United States National Recovery Administrations and National War Labor Board Printed and Mimeographed Documents 5780/085: ILGWU National War Labor Board case files 6127m: National War Labor Board Executive Meeting Transcript
Administrative agencies -- United States -- Rules and practice; Labor policy -- United States; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- United States; Wages -- Government policy -- United States; War and emergency powers -- United States; World War, 1914-1918 -- United States -- Economic aspects; Labor disputes -- United States -- State supervision; Wages -- Government policy -- United States; Boehm, Randolph.; Dubofsky, Melvyn, 1934-; United States. National War Labor Board (1918-1919)
3337352
- Resumes of Case (Reel 1)
  - Cigar Makers v. Offterdinger. Washington, DC., 1 (Reel 1)
    Scope and Contents
    1 p.
  - American Federation of Labor v. Tennessee Coal, Iron, and Railroad et al. Birmingham, Alabama., 2 (Reel 1)
  - Commercial Telegraphers et al. v. Western Union et al. New York City, NY, 3 (Reel 1)
    2p.
  - Industrial Workers et al. v. Employers Association et al. St. Louis, MO., 4 (Reel 1)
    2 pp.
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 14 v. War Department. San Antonio, TX, 5 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenter and Joiners, Local 101 v. American Propeller and Manufacturing. Baltimore, MD., 6 (Reel 1)
  - Porto Rico Agricultural Workers v. Employers. Porto Rico., 7 (Reel 1)
  - Industrial Workers v. Employers. Oshkosh, Wisconsin., 8 (Reel 1)
  - Paper Makers, Local 68 et al. v. Harley Pulp and Paper et al. Portland, Oregon., 9 (Reel 1)
  - Marine Workers Affiliation v. Boat Owners. New York City, NY., 10 (Reel 1)
  - Musical Instrument Makers, Local 1 v. Lyon and Healy. Chicago., 11 (Reel 1)
  - Miners, Local 251 v. Sloss-Sheffield Steel and Iron. Russellville, AL., 12 (Reel 1)
  - Miners' Union, Local 268 v. Thomas Iron. Wharton, NJ., 13 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Worthington Pump and Machinery. East Cambridge, MA., 14 (Reel 1)
  - United Hatters v. United States Hat. Danbury, CT., 15 (Reel 1)
  - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 226 v. St. Joseph Lead. Herculaneum, MO., 16 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Machine Shops. Bridgeport, CT., 17 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Eugene Dietzgen. Chicago., 18 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Pittsfield, Massachusetts., 19 (Reel 1)
  - Cranemen v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY., 20 (Reel 1)
  - Federal Labor Union #15543 et al. v. Hammond Lumber et al. Van Buren, Maine., 21 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists et al. Bethlehem Steel. Bethlehem, PA., 22 (Reel 1)
  - Steam Engineers, Local 45 et al. v. Joplin and Pittsburg Railway. Joplin, Mo. and Pittsburg, Ks., 23 (Reel 1)
  - Building Trades v. Bullard Machine. Bridgeport, Ct., 24 (Reel 1)
  - Tin Plate Employees, Local 31 v. Employers. Elwood, Indiana., 25 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 477 v. Philadelphia Rapid Transit. Philadelphia., 26 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Koken Barber Supply. St. Louis., 27 (Reel 1)
  - Dredgermen's Union v. Employers. San Francisco., 28 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters District Council v. General Builders Association. Detroit., 29 (Reel 1)
  - Elevator Constructors Union v. Electric Workers. Chicago., 30 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland Railway. Cleveland, Ohio, 31 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Railway Employees, Division 26 v. Detroit United Railway. Detroit., 32 (Reel 1)
  - Polishers v. Remington Arms. Bridgeport, Conn., 33 (Reel 1)
  - Molders v. Phoenix Manufacturing. Eau Claire, Wisconsin., 34 (Reel 1)
  - Papermakers et al. v. International Paper et al. New York City., 35 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 178 v. Avery Company. Peoria, Il., 36 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 818 v. Wheeling Mold and Foundry et al. Wheeling, West Virginia., 37 (Reel 1)
  - Painters, District Council 14 v. Cuthbert Boat. Chicago, Illinois., 38 (Reel 1)
  - Iron Workers v. Du Pont Engineering. Nashville, TN., 39 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists et al. v. Frick Company et al. Waynesboro, PA., 40 (Reel 1)
  - Aurora, Elgin and Chicago Railroad v. Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 215. Aurora, Illinois., 41 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 168 v. Scranton Railway. Scranton, PA., 42 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway, Division 125 v. East St. Louis and Suburban Railway et al. East St. Louis, Illinois., 43 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 576 v. Schenectady Railway. Schenectady, NY., 44 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers v. Northern Indiana Gas and Electric. Hammond, IN., 45 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 46 v. Minneapolis Steel and Machinery et al. Minneapolis., 46 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Virginia Bridge and Iron. Roanoke, VA., 47 (Reel 1)
  - Master Plumbers v. Plumbers, Gas, and Steam Fitters, Local 41. Butte, MT., 48 (Reel 1)
  - Standard Boiler and Plate Iron v. Boilermakers and Helpers, Local 363. East St. Louis, IL, and Niles, OH., 49 (Reel 1)
  - Plumbers and Steamfitters, Local 149 v. Reliable Heating and Plumbing et al. Champaign and Urbana, IL., 50 (Reel 1)
  - Hosiery Workers, Local 696 v. Henry Brown Hosiery et al. Philadelphia., 51 (Reel 1)
  - Cleveland Osborn Manufacturing v. Cleveland Building Trades. Cleveland., 52 (Reel 1)
  - Stove Mounters, Local 8 v. Estate Stove. Hamilton, OH., 53 (Reel 1)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute in Cigar Makers' Council. New York., 54 (Reel 1)
  - Sheffield Iron v. Employees. Sheffield, AL., 55 (Reel 1)
  - Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers v. Kingsport Fiber et al. Kingsport, TN and Bristol and Buena Vista, VA., 56 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 380 v. Cleveland, Southwestern and Columbus Railway. Elyria, Oh., 57 (Reel 1)
  - Bridge and Iron Workers, Local 214 v. Fort Pitt Bridge Works. Canonsburg, PA., 58 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 241 and 308 v. Chicago Surface Lines et al. Chicago., 59 (Reel 1)
  - Coopers, Local 193 v. Wooden Tank Manufacturers. Chicago., 60 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. American Locomotive. Schenectady, NY., 61 (Reel 1)
  - Painters Union 47 et al. v. Master House Painters et al. Indianapolis., 62 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, District Lodge 1 v. Hess Bright Manufacturing. Philadelphia., 63 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 198 v. General Contractors. Dallas, Texas., 64 (Reel 1)
  - Journeymen Bookbinders, Local 4 v. US Government Printing Office, Washington DC., 65 (Reel 1)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Policemen's Benevolent Association v. Pennsylvania Railroad Police Dept. New York Division., 66 (Reel 1)
  - Building Construction Employers Association v. Steam and Operating Engineers. Chicago., 67 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Nordyke and Marmon. Indianapolis., 68 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Public Service Railway. Newark, NJ., 69 (Reel 1)
  - Boatmen v. Owners of Steamboat Alabama of the Old Bay line. Baltimore, MD., 70 (Reel 1)
  - Boilermakers, Local 592 v. Kansas City Structural Steel et al. Tulsa, OK., 71 (Reel 1)
  - Portland Railway, Light, and Power v. Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 757. Portland, OR., 72 (Reel 1)
  - Youngstown and Ohio River Railroad v. Street and Electric Railway Employees. Leetonia, OH., 73 (Reel 1)
  - Lever Brothers v. Carpenters District Council. Boston., 74 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Elyria and Cleveland Railroad. Cleveland., 75 (Reel 1)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Locals 35 and 50 v. Iron League Erector's Association. New York City., 76 (Reel 1)
  - Crafts Affiliated with the Michigan Federation of Labor v. Packard Motor Car, Detroit., 77 (Reel 1)
  - Crafts Affiliated with the Michigan Federation of Labor v. Lincoln Motor Car. Detroit., 78 (Reel 1)
  - Cold Storage Warehouse Workers v. Pier House et al. Chicago., 79 (Reel 1)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen v. Western Cold Storage. Chicago., 80 (Reel 1)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 566 v. Wilson Provision et al. Peoria, IL., 81 (Reel 1)
  - Sheep Shearers, Fremont County, WY v. J.M. Wilson, Wool Grower, Douglas, WY., 82 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 735 v. Jacksonville Traction. Jacksonville, FL., 83 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 528 v. U.S. Washington, DC., 84 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers v. TA Gillespie Company. South Amboy, NJ., 85 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 429 v. Du Pont Powder. Nashville, TN., 86 (Reel 1)
  - Chicago Foundry men's Assoc. v. Molders. Chicago., 87 (Reel 1)
  - Flour Mill Employees, Union 15974 v. Pittsburg Elevator et al. Pittsburg, KS. Cooks, Waiters, and Waitresses, Local 748 v. Sundry Proprietors of Cafes and Restaurants. Fort Worth, TX., 88 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Mark Manufacturing. Evanston, IL., 89 (Reel 1)
  - Journeyman Masons v. Employers. West Point and Highland Falls, New York., 90 (Reel 1)
  - Merchant and Evans v. Union Machinists. Philadelphia., 91 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 802 v. Kansas City and Western Railway. Leavenworth, KS., 92 (Reel 1)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. Southern California Iron and Steel. Los Angeles., 93 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Willys-Overland. Elyria, OH., 94 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 132 and 148 v. United Traction. Albany, NY., 95 (Reel 1)
  - Boilermakers et al. v. National Refining. Coffeyville, KS., 96 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 194 v. New Orleans Railway and Light. New Orleans., 97 (Reel 1)
  - Fire Department v. City of St. Louis., 98 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 465 v. Employers. San Diego., 99 (Reel 1)
  - Brick Layers v. Hampton and Company. San Diego., 100 (Reel 1)
  - Blacksmiths, Local 42 v. Pollak Steel. Cincinnati., 101 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Philadelphia Belting. Philadelphia., 102 (Reel 1)
  - Building Trades Employers' Association v. Hod Carriers, Building, and Common Laborers, local 10. Cleveland., 103 (Reel 1)
  - Printing Pressmen and Assistants, Local 4 v. Franklin Division of Franklin-Typothetae. Chicago., 104 (Reel 1)
  - Federal Labor Union 16104 v. Emerson Brantingham Manufacturing et al. Batavia, IL., 105 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 108 v. Bethlehem Shipbuilding. Fore River Yards., 106 (Reel 1)
  - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 266 v. Trenton Smelter and Refining. Trenton, NJ., 107 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 515 v. Galesburg Railway, Lighting, and Power. Galesburg, IL., 108 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Red Star Milling et al. Wichita, KS., 109 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 64 v. Mason Machine Works. Taunton, MA., 110 (Reel 1)
  - Oil Field Workers Union 15940 v. Employers. Montebello, CA., 111 (Reel 1)
  - Masters, Mates, and Pilots v. Cornell Shipbuilding. Camden, NJ., 112 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Lowell Gas and Light Company. Lowell, MA., 113 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 244 v. Central Specialty Company et al. Detroit., 114 (Reel 1)
  - Bookbinders, Local 7 v. US Government Printing Office, Washington, DC., 115 (Reel 1)
  - General Strike, Bloomington, IL., 116 (Reel 1)
  - Foundry Workers v. Employers. Detroit., 117 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 244 v. US Department of the Interior. Grand Junction, CO., 118 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 282, 580, and 532 v. New York State Railways. Rochester, NY., 119 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Hamilton Machine Tool. Hamilton, OH., 120 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 330 v. Russell Motor Car. Buffalo, NY., 121 (Reel 1)
  - Hydraulic Press Manufacturing Company v. Babcock and Wilcox Company et al. Barberton, OH., 122 (Reel 1)
  - Central Labor Union v. Price Fireproofing. Poughkeepsie, NY., 123 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Suwanee Iron Company. Russellville, AL., 124 (Reel 1)
  - Federal Labor Union 15338 v. Magnolia Petroleum Company. Beaumont, TX., 125 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY., 126 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 218 v. Cleveland Steel Castings Company et al. Cleveland., 127 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. Midvale Steel and Ordnance, Philadelphia., 128 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Corn Products Refining Company. Granite City, IL., 129 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Pennsylvania-New Jersey Railway. Trenton, NJ., 130 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Locals 30, 782 and 826 v. Employers, Bridgeport, Connecticut., 131 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Linemen, Local 30 v. Erie Lighting Company et al. Erie, PA., 132 (Reel 1)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. AM Byers. Girard, Ohio., 133 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Salt Lake Iron Steel. Salt Lake City, UT., 134 (Reel 1)
  - Building Trades Employers Association. Chicago, IL., 135 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters v. C.A. Dodge. Cambridge, MA., 136 (Reel 1)
  - Timbermen v. Warsau Southern Lumber Company. Laurel, MS., 137 (Reel 1)
  - Metal Mine Workers v. Silver Bow Employers Association. Butte, MT., 138 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Employers. Cleveland, OH., 139 (Reel 1)
  - Molders v. Canton Steel Foundry. Canton, OH., 140 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Employers, Kokomo, IN., 141 (Reel 1)
  - Foundrymen v. Grey Iron Club. Brooklyn, NY., 142 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Putnam Machine, Fitchburg, MA., 143 (Reel 1)
  - Textile Workers v. Lowell Mill Treasurers. Lowell, MA., 144 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 817 et al. v. Columbus Railway, Power and Light. Columbus, OH., 145 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Jackson and Church et al. Saginaw, Michigan., 146 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists v. Jersey City machinery. Jersey City, NJ., 147 (Reel 1)
  - Master Roofers Association, Local 161 v. Naval Station et al. Boston, MA and Vicinity., 148 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 806, 810, and 749 v. City Railroad et al. Dayton, OH., 149 (Reel 1)
  - Inquiry of City Button Works. New York City., 150 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 623 v. International Railway. Buffalo, NY., 151 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 350 v. Schoelkopf Chemical. Buffalo, NY., 152 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 807 et al. v. Omaha and Council Bluffs Street Railway. Omaha, NE., 153 (Reel 1)
  - Oil and Gas Well Workers, Local 15503 v. Employers. Taft, CA., 154 (Reel 1)
  - Brotherhood of Drop Forge Trades v. Remington Arms et al. Bridgeport, CT. (Also all craftsmen in same industries throughout the country)., 155 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 196 v. United Engineering and Foundry. Youngstown, OH., 156 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Triangle Pattern and Manufacturing et al. Detroit, MI., 157 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 732 v. Georgia Railway and Power. Atlanta., 158 (Reel 1)
  - Molders, Local 81 v. A.F. Brown et al. Elizabethtown, NJ., 159 (Reel 1)
  - Envelope, Paper Box, and Paper Bag Association v. Samuel Cupples Envelope Company. St. Louis., 160 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Employers. East Providence Rhode Island., 161 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists et al. v. Worthington Pump and Machinery. Cudahy, WI., 162 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. Fox Brothers Manufacturing et al. St. Louis MO., 163 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 164 v. Wilkes-Barre Railway. Wilkes-Barre, PA., 164 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Corn Products Company. Argo, IL., 165 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland and Eastern Traction, Cleveland, OH., 166 (Reel 1)
  - Painters, Local 28 v. Gahogen Shipyard et al. Long Island City, NY., 167 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Middletown Car. Middletown, PA., 168 (Reel 1)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers et al. v. National Enameling and Stamping. Granite City, IL and St. Louis, MO., 169 (Reel 1)
  - Auto Tire Builders and Finishers Federal Labor Union 16159 v. Ehman Tire and Rubber. Chicago., 170 (Reel 1)
  - Employers v. Machinists. Akron, OH., 171 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 746 v. Denver City Tramway. Denver., 172 (Reel 1)
  - Federal Labor Union 15047 v. Union Carbide. Sault Ste. Marie, MI., 173 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 805 v. East St. Louis, Columbia, and Waterloo Railway. East St. Louis, IL., 174 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Standard Wheel. Terre Haute, IN., 175 (Reel 1)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 601 v. Hammond Packing et al. Pittsburgh and McKeesport, PA., 176 (Reel 1)
  - Metal Trades Council v. Ajax Iron Works et al. Denver., 177 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Joseph M. Mason Machine. Philadelphia., 178 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 618 v. Rhode Island Company. Providence, RI., 179 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 589 v. Boston Elevated Railway. Boston., 180 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Hannan Slocum Company. Newark, NJ., 181 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Employers. Toledo, OH., 182 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Archibald Wheel Company. Lawrence, MA., 183 (Reel 1)
  - Leather Workers v. National Leather Belting et al. New York City., 184 (Reel 1)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute between Iron Workers Union and Plumbers Union. Boston., 185 (Reel 1)
  - Ladies Garment Workers, Local 26, 27, 29, 37, and 42 v. Manufacturers. Cleveland, Ohio., 186 (Reel 1)
  - Jewelry Workers, Local 18 v. Jewelry Manufacturers. Attleboro, MA., 187 (Reel 1)
  - Central Federated Union v. National metal Trades Association. Providence, RI., 188 (Reel 1)
  - Oil and Gas Workers, Local 16107 v. Employers, Martinez, CA., 189 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. American International Shipbuilding et al. Boston, Gloucester, NJ, and Philadelphia., 190 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 725 v. Birmingham Railway, Light and Power. Birmingham, AL., 191 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland, Painesville, and Eastern Railroad et al. Cleveland., 192 (Reel 1)
  - Ferguson Steel and Iron v. Carpenters and Joiners. Buffalo, NY., 193 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists et al. v. Employers. Madison, WI., 194 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees v. Twin City Rapid Transit Company et al. St. Paul, MN., 195 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 761 v. Springfield Consolidated. Springfield, IL., 196 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. American Steel. Franklin, PA., 197 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters v. Imperial Shipbuilding. Detroit, MI., 198 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 55 v. Superior Tool. Columbus, OH., 199 (Reel 1)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 524 and 165 v. North Western Fuel et al. Superior, WI., 200 (Reel 1)
  - Tobacco Workers v. American Tobacco. Louisville, KY., 201 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 669 v. Auburn and Syracuse Electric Railroad. Auburn, NY., 202 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Metal Trades Employers. Birmingham, AL., 203 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 713 v. Memphis Street Railway, Memphis, TN., 204 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 738 v. Cincinnati and Dayton Traction. Dayton, OH., 205 (Reel 1)
  - Montana Metal Trades v. Anaconda Copper. Great Falls, MT., 206 (Reel 1)
  - Hazel Glass Company v. Employees. Washington, PA and Wheeling, WV., 207 (Reel 1)
  - Federal Employees v. US Navy Department. Washington, DC., 208 (Reel 1)
  - Conductors, Trainmen, and Engineers v. Interurban Lines. Portland, OR., 209 (Reel 1)
  - Stove Mounters, Local 1 v. Michigan Stove et al. Detroit MI., 210 (Reel 1)
  - Hod Carriers, Local 407 v. US Naval Torpedo Station. Newport, RI., 211 (Reel 1)
  - Colored Bag Men and Mail Porters v. Employers. Philadelphia., 212 (Reel 1)
  - Railroad Trainmen, Local 808 et al. v. Pacific Electric Railway. Los Angeles., 213 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists Local 398 v. American Standard Metal Products. Bordertown, NJ., 214 (Reel 1)
  - Carpenters, Local 14 et al. v. Thomas Harmon et al. San Antonio, TX., 215 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Colt Firearms, Hartford, CT., 216 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Charles Perkes. Philadelphia., 217 (Reel 1)
  - Pattern Makers v. Bethlehem Steel. Sparrows Point, MD., 218 (Reel 1)
  - Metal Polishers, Local 2 v. Employers. Toledo, OH., 219 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Local 161 v. Kleiber-Dawson Machine. Indianapolis., 220 (Reel 1)
  - Machinists, Lodge 364 v. Holt Manufacturing. Stockton, CA., 221 (Reel 1)
  - Women Employees v. Chevrolet. Bay City, MI., 222 (Reel 1)
  - Federal Labor Unions 16067 and 16135 v. Employers. Madison, WI. Boilermakers v. American Locomotive. Richmond, VA., 223 (Reel 1)
  - Firefighters v. Municipal Government. Pittsburgh, PA., 224 (Reel 1)
  - Hotel, Restaurant, and Bartenders Organization v. Hotel and Restaurant Employers. Chicago., 225 (Reel 1)
  - Express Drivers v. American Railway Express. Columbus, Ohio., 226 (Reel 1)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 228 v. Chicago and Joliet Electric Railway. Joliet, IL., 227 (Reel 1)
  - Hardwood Finishers, Local 426 et al. v. Manufacturers of Interior Work. Philadelphia., 228 (Reel 1)
  - Lynn Central Labor Union et al. v. General Electric. Lynn, MA., 229 (Reel 1)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. American Sheet and Tin Plate. Elwood, IN., 230 (Reel 1)
  - Laundry Workers, Local 36 v. Imperial Laundry, et al. Little Rock, AR., 231 (Reel 1)
  - Inquiry of Warren Steam Pump Company. Warren, MA., 232 (Reel 1)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 468 v. Decker and Sons. Mason City, IA., 233 (Reel 1)
  - Shoe Cutters v. Brockton Shoe Manufacturers. Brockton, MA., 234 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Millville Rubber. Millville, MA., 235 (Reel 1)
  - Railway Conductors, Division 337 v. Washington, Baltimore and Annapolis Electric Railway. Baltimore, MD., 236 (Reel 1)
  - Employees v. Virginia Bridge and Iron. Memphis, TN., 237 (Reel 1)
  - Employees Association v. Brooklyn Rapid Transit. Brooklyn, NY., 238 (Reel 1)